<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidITRI</string>
    <string name="guide_introduction">Guide introduction</string>
    <string name="origin_exhibition">Origins of the exhibition</string>
    <string name="tour_title">Choose guide</string>
    <string name="rules_automated_guid">Rules for the automated guide </string>
    <string name="survey_1_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="survey_title">Visitor information</string>
    <string name="origin_content"><![CDATA[The Architecture and Building Research Institute, Ministry of the Interior, has long promoted “smart buildings” to humanize space and improve the quality of living environments through integration of building design and information technology. \n\nTo give the public an understanding and experience smart living, the Architecture and Building Research Institute constructed the Living 3.0 Smart Home Space Exhibition Center in 2008 as a training base for Taiwan’s smart building education. The objective is to promote smart building concepts, provide functional experience, and create new opportunities for integration of domestic IT industry with other industries. \n\n
    The theme of this exhibition center is “humanized care, innovative technology, prospective living, environmental protection and energy conservation, and smart sustainability.” This exhibition integrated diverse smart technology and innovative IT automatic sensor and control technology. Scenario and demonstration systems were set up to let the public experience different smart home and office space scenarios. The goal is to create prospective living environment and quality.]]></string>
    <string name="tour_content"><![CDATA[This exhibition center has two floors that are open to visitors. The first floor is the home space scenario while the second floor is the office scenario. Over 200 smart devices were introduced and a total of 90 domestic vendors participated in this event. Of the devices on site, 95% are already in commercial development. Visitors are welcome to experience hands-on certain scenario applications and equipment. \n\nThere are three guide avatars in the tour guide system. Visitors can freely choose the one they like to conduct the automated tour and introduce them to smart living.]]></string>
    <string name="rule_content"><![CDATA[To maintain visitors’ rights and tour quality, we remind you to follow the below rules:<br>
    <h5><font color=#303F9F>*Environmental quality: </font></h5><b>1.</b> No eating or drinking allowed in the exhibition. Please check in all food and drinks at the service desk. <br><br><b>2.</b> Please turn all mobile phones to silent and avoid speaking loudly. No shouting is allowed in the exhibition.<br>
    <h5><font color=#303F9F>*Guide tablet: </font></h5><b>1.</b> The tablet is only for guide use and is not open for connecting to external networks. Please do not use any digital tools to upload or download any digital data. <br><br><b>2.</b> The tablet has built in positioning system, please do not take it out of the exhibition area (shown in the map). If visitors need to use the restroom, please give the tablet to the service desk personnel for safekeeping. If visitors accidentally take the tablet out of the exhibition hall, exhibition hall personnel will make contact with the person who checked out the tablet. <br><br><b>2.</b> When the automated guide ends, please remember to return the tablet to the service desk and retrieve your ID. Please make sure the table PC is operating normally.<br>
    <h5><font color=#303F9F>*Exhibition facility equipment: </font></h5><b>1.</b> Exhibition facilities and equipment that are labeled “Operable” can be operated and experienced by on-site visitors. <br><br><b>2.</b> If individuals cause serious damage to exhibition facilities and equipment during the automated guide process, the visitor who caused the damage shall be liable for repairs.]]></string>
</resources>